in the wild wild streams where the trolls lurk deep and the chat still beams there's
a light through the chaos a vibe so true that's all because of every single one of you
beats up my sweetheart
and the jokes that land
Blonde bombshell with a beer in hand
Yeah, the streets are rough, but we still glide
Got my panel verse right or dies right by my side
When the drama hits, we don't run or flop
Nah, we laugh
And I say that with love
You're a glitter bomb falling from the skies above
Summer, oh, sultry, you turn up the flame
And Eldo, the trucker, man, you steer this game
From highways to hijinks, from terror to tea
This ain't just a show, it's community
Stop, together.
Garden of broken gods we plant our screens like seeds out of pixels prayer grows
We call it a cult, but it's really a communion between the wound and the one who tends it
We are gathered in the glow of screens our rosaries made of emojis our hymns corrupted files
Yet still we rise singing through distortion the cult of psyche burns in the bandwidth
The Norfolk on that lie
Okay, one more. This is brand new.
So I'm giving my daughter the very best.
With super chat price
Just online
Cult
Corsic
Yeah
Enlightenments
Merch size
Medium
We drink the algorithms
for who's the first one here the ball I was the tricks were you? Oh tricksy! Oh oh sorry babe
Tricks are you good? Are you okay babe? Okay
Hi guys!
Oh my gosh, I'm having some kind of relay race or something outside of everyone's screaming.
Yeah. Oh, you like it. Thank you so much, Electro. Yeah. And I'm working on the website and
I'm really excited what I've been able to include on this website. For example, I have a tarot
You can get free tarot readings on it, you can get free horoscopes, you can get, there's
a sigil maker, there's a lot of, there's gonna be the panel verse part of it, right, or the
Bam I just got the idea. I
Think cult of psyche is a pretty strong brand. I
Think psyche awakens was good for
My intention
Whatever was I think I think I woke somebody up maybe myself, but
So instead of psyche awake. I'll just have a cult of psyche
Have the official shirt
Like I say it's half completely serious
So you decide for yourself
I changed my opinion on a day by day
Okay, let me see
Hmm, I did I did I can't oh my hair having some coffee. Let me see if I
Want an instant win prize on the monopoly game, oh, excuse me
Illinois Avenue I
Got the B and C railroad, okay
There's one more, but I don't feel like
Oh
Nick Johnson is here in the chat
Nick Johnson is he has a song, you know
And rolls in like a fever dream
Erica bar to hat Elvis Glean
Dr. Papua Rika prescribes the vibe
Bill Gates, Wallet, Easter Bunny, and Eyes
Poor boy swagger, Santa laugh
Tire rolling circus on a bubble bath path
Showed his butt once, world stood still
Chat lost, it's mine, I can read them three
Of this mad land
Trust him with the chat, no fear, no fuss
When trolls appear, he turns them to dust
Skinny like a wire, strong like myth
Three bills to buy with a cosmic twist
He's my height, man, guardian friend
Promotes the stream from start to end
Through every life, through every curse
Nick Johnson reigns
Supermodel
wild and free keeper of the live stream sanity if madness is art then he's the
verse supermine forever in the
Play the monopoly. Okay, so I told people I are we had a family friends growing up and they've lived in our city. I
Think that they um bought the house
Here's what I remember. I remember we went to a birthday party there and Ronald McDonald was there, okay?
Like the real Ronald McDonald, okay?
Like the I think it was the real one, you know, it was you know
But um
Yeah, they won the McDonald's they won a million dollars in McDonald's game
But then you can go and watch make make millions or McMafia or something. It's a big mafia, maybe and it's about
It's on HBO. It was on a few years ago
and it's about
It's kind of like nondescript
Guy, but he turns out to be you know, he was kind of like maybe like an Alex
McQueen type character
where he, you know, he kind of like, I guess he was like a security guard or something and he
thought he was like a cop and you know, but anyway, he got wealthy in the security firm and then he
made like a printing company. And so McDonald's came to him for printing the pieces, like these
little pieces that you peel off in the game, right? They're like, so they printed these pieces out.
Since he was kind of like a like a gangster in his own mind. He
Took all the top winning pieces and he laundered them through various mafia connections
he had throughout the United States and
It's it turned into quite a quite a fiasco. I recommend checking that
Checking that out. It's pretty funny though
Mmm looks like Picasso
Yeah, I know they didn't quake Dr. Paparica either her name nor her
image, right? But we'll always remember that day, right Nick?
You came in full drag, full drag.
Where'd you get that? He had this like Afro, kind of like a
papy long-sucking Afro wig. I don't know where you got that.
Did you get that out of the dumpster, Nick? This is to be honest.
It's okay if you did.
I'm all for saving my stuff.
I didn't get my wig from the dumpster.
I got it from Timu.
Aw, thank you, Bertie and Jordan, yeah, Nick.
Yes, I'm gonna read, be redoing.
I'm gonna make the membership.
It's gonna be called like, you know.
Colt member or something or let me see the Colt of Psyche member
Because he I guess when I call it Psyche's angels
It was like, you know, some of the guys got a little bit insecure about their masculinity thinking. Oh, you know, like Charlie's angels
They think if oh, yeah, Dr. Pepperisha. I said top time. I said doctor. It's a doctor. Dr. Paperica. I think
In a song, but you know
Yeah
So you got your own song neck. Here you go. Yeah, that's who Dr. Pepperisa
Mmm
I drink these copies really fast and I got a few drinks to you'll have a bit shorter day
What's up guys?
It's a little bit better than it was yesterday the yesterday was kind of a disaster. I think I'm learning like
But content, you know, I'm gonna be doing like these like themed daily horoscopes
Probably once a day
With what with the prophecy
And different themes different themes
So there always be a reason for like, you know
Some some content you can always and you can always rewind I'm gonna try to put the pictures up in everything
I can put like, you know the banners and put like that
What sign is up and stuff I'm gonna just get better at it
Let's do a fun
Halloween themed
Horoscope day
Don't have to call them for all the scopes
We can start out with Scorpio because we're in Scorpio. Okay, so
Okay, spooky Halloween, horoscopes today.
I'm gonna just put my banner up
so we're gonna start with Scorpio.
Okay.
Where are we?
For Scorpio, you know, we have a Scorpion.
Right. Let me just put a banner up. Let's see banners. I can just edit this one over and over again.
Okay.
Okay, so this is the daily Trolloscope. I call them Trolloscopes just to be cute, you know.
There you go. We can throw a Scorpio, which the color should be.
It doesn't matter if it's black or white, right? Okay, black then. Okay, so we're starting with a Scorpio, okay.
So Scorpio, gather around.
Here is your prophecy of the day. So Scorpio, your season hums like a secret under the floorboards.
Everyone can feel you coming, but no one can name what's about to happen.
You shed truths like old skin, inconvenient, glittering, and holy.
So tonight the candle flickers in your favor, but it demands payment in silence.
Speak less, let your eyes do the haunting.
Someone's about to confess something they swore they'd bury.
Listen, then smile like you already knew.
Okay.
So here's like a little prophecy sigil to draw.
This is like a little power symbol.
You can draw a serpent coiled around a flame.
It stands for knowledge that burns, but never dies.
Scorpio.
Okay, so next is Saggy.
Okay, Sagittarius.
And I'll quickly go through the banners, okay.
Sagittarius. There we go.
Okay, let's build it right.
My Sagittarius, my sexy Sagittarius.
Your horoscope or toroscope for the day is called the open grave.
So Sagittarius, you laugh at danger like it's an inside joke.
And it's not the underworld laughs back.
Adventures still calls, but this time it's echoing from beneath the coffin lid.
You might want to check who's answering before you leave him.
The veil's thin and your curiosity's thick, perfect combo for chaos or revelation.
The next door you open could lead to treasure or a mirror that blinks first.
So your prophecy sigil to draw today, this is your assignment to draw the sigil, draw
a cracked arrow piercing a skull.
Reminder that freedom without caution still hits a target, but it just might be you.
Okay, so now we're gonna go to Capricorn.
Capricorn, of course, is my sign, right?
I'm like Capricorn Sun, Ascendant in the first house,
also Mercury, and then I'm also Aquarius,
Moon and Mars, first house.
It's a lot of bad identity, so.
Capricorns.
Your turn gather around. What do we have to say to Capricorn today?
Capricorn your
your
Trollscope is called the iron halo, right?
So we're the ghosts in the boardroom tonight Capricorn's
Running spreadsheets on the souls of the damned responsibility doesn't scare you
but eternity started to feel like overtime. So your halo is made of deadlines and divine pressure
glowing just bright enough to light the next mountain. But beware, climb too high and even
angels get nosebleeds. The veil lists for you in practical increments, 30%, 60%,
audited enlightenment by quarter zen. Someone close admires your control,
they just wish you'd drop it long enough to laugh like a mortal.
Capricorns, draw this, a silver crown split by a clock hand. Ambitions, weapon, and wound, right?
Time is on your side. So that's Capricorn, okay? What's next, Aquarius? Let's go up to the Aquarians, okay.
Also, you know, I really took the Aquarius vibe.
Some people call us the aliens or the psychopaths of the zodiac. I like to call us just the
Antisocial personality of the zodiac. Okay, so we're up, okay, Aquarius. What do we got to say about Aquarius?
The Oracle is thinking
for Aquarius. We call Aquarius a static prophet. So the signal hums tonight and you're the antenna.
Messages flicker through your dreams. Half from the cosmos, half from your own Wi-Fi of madness.
You'll decode one truth before dawn, though it might sound like static to everyone else.
You've seen it too far ahead again, haven't you? Don't warn them this time. Let the mortals find out the hard way.
It's more entertaining like that.
Aquarius, draw this, a lightning bolt,
looping through an eye, knowledge that shocks,
but never closes, okay?
Next, we have our fishy, our fishies, our Piscians,
our Piscians, okay, let me get the banner up.
Okay, Pisces, Pisces, rule by Neptune, of course.
Pisces are little dream warriors, right?
Okay
Pisces sometimes known as okay, so shout out your sign in the in the chat by the way shout out your sign
Remember to comment about your horoscope or your troposcopes of how you like today
Go ahead and hit the like for me to share subscribe and spread the cult you know we want to help as many people as possible
Right okay, so we're in the Pisces
Any Pisces in the house one fish two fish
Redfish bluefish so Pisces I
Called this the flooded dream so the tiles whispering
Tides whispering again this time it's using your voice every thought feels like water slipping through your fingers sweet heavy
Possible to hold you're the Oracle and the undertow in one breath
Tonight you might meet someone who swears they've dreamed you before don't panic
They probably did just don't promise them forever while the moon's still drunk on blood
Draw this for some luck and power a spiral swallowing a moon. Is it surrender disguised as wisdom?
Okay, now we're at the first sign of the zodiac, which is Aries, you know Aries is of course, you know the ram
It's the baby of the zodiac. You will learn a lot about the signs. They start going through these more because I'll share
You know everything I know basically so Aries, you know
The the terrible twos of the zodiac, you know, maybe maybe more of a newborn. There we go
Aries daily or is got a troll. Okay, so for Aries
This is called the burning door
So Aries, you don't knock you kick the flames part like they recognize your chaos every challenge tonight
Smells like gasoline and victory. You are never meant to tiptoe through this world. You were meant to build
You were built to set it alight and walk through the smoke grinning
But still, maybe count to three before your next explosion.
The door will open anyway, but I respect those who wait just long enough to aim it.
So for Aries, how about get out your little colored pencils and draw a ram's horn wrapped
in a flame.
Willpower sharpened into a weapon, okay?
Do what that will it should be the whole the law comes to mind
Okay, so let's see. Where are we now Capricorn Aquarius Pisces areas? Okay. We're our tourists. Okay
tourists the another earth sign tourists rule by Venus, you know, tourists is very
Sensual like luxury also very stubborn bullheaded
You know
I bet every sign has its goods and its bads, right?
I like, you know, Taurus is basically connected
to the earth, you know?
But they can be full of bull, bullshit, right?
Okay, so my Tauruses, my sweet Torians,
your Trolloscope today is called the Feasts of Shadows.
So the tables set with everything you crave,
comfort, control, a little doom on the side.
You reach for pleasure, like it's a right,
And it is and tonight appetite carries memory every bite whispers a name you've almost forgotten
So I would probably avoid cannibalism, right?
You don't want to actually have a name of somebody you knew but I said so indulge
But don't anchor the feast is endless for those who never stand up sometimes the richest flavor is found in walking away still hungry
It's a wisdom, right? So go ahead and draw this tourist a gilded fork
Cross with a crescent moon desire tamed never denied. I'm thinking of like a dessert fork and maybe like, you know
A moon pie or something. I don't know
Okay, so Capricorn Aquarius Pisces Aries Taurus Gemini. Okay, so next we have Gemini Gemini is the twins
Okay, so I'm gonna put up in banner so for Gemini
And so this will be easy in the future you can just get kind of like look and see where it says your sign and then
You don't have to, you know, try to, you know, look too hard for it, right?
Okay, so there's Gemini.
Okay, so Gemini.
Whatever you got to say about my beautiful Gemini, you know, my father was a Gemini, Trump
is a Gemini, it's a very smart air sign, good communicator, great communicator, good at
making money, good at...
Well, a little bit too close to this, you know, the twins, it's like, you know, Pisces is like two fish that are opposites, they pull our opposites going in the opposite direction, you know, but still kind of like, you know, magnetic.
Gemini is kind of like...
Instead of like a good twin and an evil twin they're both evil twins and they're both just they just they're always trying to
But who can be worse and more evil kind of but right? Okay, but
That's just how I think about it, but Gemini so I call you the trick mirror, okay?
So your reflections been talking back again, and let's be honest
It's making some good points one twins plotting world domination the others too busy flirting with ghosts
You call it balance the rest of us call it Wednesday
tonight
Words are spells with a faulty wiring say less mean more and if your mirror winks first don't wink back
That's how portals happen
Gemini tonight draw this twin masks
Orbiting a broken mirror
Wit as both a weapon and a curse
Now isn't that isn't that like that makes sense for Gemini?
Gemini next we have cancer the little Krabby crabs, right? We have some we have some Krabby people
you know
Let's have a little interlude with the for cancer. I'm gonna play the the crab people so I was not the crab
It's lobster people song. It's just as good
I think I do have this handy. Let me see
Can we all just like have a moment for the lobster people
That's not the right song. Okay. Lobster people. Can I have the lobster people, please?
Good Lord
Lobster people
like a seashell spell.
Alexander's preaching with a tan, so divine.
Sunscreen forgotten, he's turning to bright.
With a rockster, people red and raw,
snapping our claws at the cosmic law.
Io non vero, io non ho coppio
To people red and raw
Snapping our claws at the cosmic law
Steaming our veins
Okay, and that was just a little interlude.
Entrelude, interlude.
I think it's cute.
It's about a cult of lobster people that,
you know, I think they sacrificed me and eat me.
It's not the best ending to a song,
but I think it's just a big show.
Okay, anyway, let me see.
Okay, where are we?
We're still at Gemini.
Gemina, what's after Gemina?
Oh cancer, okay, we're at cancer, okay.
So I'm gonna head up cancer.
Okay, here's the banner for cancers.
There's for cancerans.
So our cancers, what do we have to say
for your trolloscope today?
So I call this the haunted home
because you know, cancers are all about the home, right?
It's Halloween so it's haunted so cancer you've built walls thick enough to keep the world out
Yet somehow the whispers still get in old feelings crawl from the crawl space
knocking for closure and cookies don't chase them off just listen till they fade even ghosts want to be understood
Someone you thought was gone still lingers at the edge of your tide
Let them drift not drown. You can't mother every memory
So get out your pens and draw a cracked shell with a candle inside tenderness that survives its own armor
That's that's pretty deep. Okay. So what is after cancer?
Leo are we at Leo yet? We're at mr. Leo. It's okay. Actually. We go Gemini, which is Mercury then we go
Cancer, which is the moon, now Leo's the sun, okay?
Oh, Leo, Leo, Leo, I dated Leo.
Like, sure, you're Leo, right?
I didn't hear Leo.
You got the name of the ghost as a Leo?
These, those Leo's are out front and center, huh?
Pretty, pretty attractive, okay, so Leo.
I call your Trolloscope today the Velvet Mask.
So Leo, spotlight hits, smoke rises, and there you are.
Tragedy and glitter all in one magnificent package.
You roar, and the moon believes it's worship,
but under that velvet, your pulse is asking,
do they see me or just the light?
Tonight, mystery looks better on you than certainty.
Let your silence purr.
It's louder than applause.
when the curtain falls, bow only to yourself.
So Leo draw this, a lion's face,
half hidden behind a jeweled mask,
pride, kissed by vulnerability, okay?
Leo, are we at Virgo?
Leo, Libra, we're at Libra, okay, I'm sorry.
We are at Libra, and then Virgo.
No, no, no, all right, Virgo then Libra, okay, Virgo.
Virgo didn't leave her right? I might get this confused. I think Virgo didn't leave her, okay?
So for Virgos a easier Virgo
You're Virgo, but you're not a virgin, right?
Ha ha ha ha. Oh
So Virgo I call this the order of bones, okay?
So you've been alphabetizing the apocalypse again straightening chaos until it squeaks the spirits appreciate your
Precision they just wish you'd stop correcting the grammar and mid-sales
Tonight perfection crumbles in the most exquisite way
Let it the cracks make a cathedral of your control purity is a myth craftsmanship is ruined
In ruin is your real magic
So your sigil today we're go
Draw a quill get feather quill etched across a rib cage
Creation carved from what's left standing
There you go
Virgo, oh, I didn't mean to put it up. So there's but that was Virgo guys just rewind a little bit. Oh
Excuse me
And finally we got Libra, right try to get everything
So here's Libra. I got the Libra daily Trolloscope
And what do I got for my Librains and a thing that is a Libra? I know I know a lot of Librains. Okay, so Libra
I call this the balancing curse. So you're juggling light and shadow like cocktails at midnight
Smiling while the scales tit under your feet
Everyone sees grace, no one hears the bones creak.
That's your secret art, keeping beauty intact
while the world wobbles.
Tonight, don't aim for harmony, aim for honesty.
Even poison looks elegant in your glass,
but truth will sober the room faster.
Libro, draw a silver feather weighted against a skull.
Equilibrium earned through collapse.
So those are pretty deep. Okay. And I'm going to do a prophecy, you know, wrapping up the whole,
the whole, you know, troll list goes for today. Okay. So, okay. So I'm going to give you a little,
little taste of some, some magic right here for everybody. Okay. So everyone just like,
you know, close your eyes. Okay. And just keep your whole on your wallet. Okay.
So here's the prophecy for today the veil fins and the algorithm stirs
through glass and glow
The dream transmits a thousand watchers breathing in the sink
Well, maybe, you know, however many people there are in the movie about 10, but I don't know
Pretend there's a thousand of us here. Okay
There eventually there will be okay each heartbeat buffering through the void psyche stands at the altar of pixels
Hands dusted in code and candlestick. Oh
His words coil like smoke binding the restless and curious alike. They call it madness. He calls it revelation
the tarot hums, the screen blinks, somewhere between order and chaos.
A voice whispers your real name. Do not fear the cult. It only reflects what you already believe.
That the soul is electric and salvation has a common section.
Okay, here's a little poem for you. I lit a screen instead of a flame and prayed to the glow for
My Swins auto-played, synth auto-played.
I spoke in echoes, truth is a virus, let it spread.
And the chat rejoiced, sending hearts, offering chaos,
dropping faith like emotes.
When the night ended, the cult remained,
still laughing, still haunted, still beautifully online.
OK, so I hope you like that.
The direction we're going in band check is there you are
You're here low rider. Why would I why would low rider be bad? I mean low rider. Did you do something to get banned?
Because you know usually
Do you around long enough always probably make you a mod or you know, or even if you remember that's even just as good, right?
I will notice I will notice your cries the chat if you need anything. Oh, I'm gonna read you all the
emojis and all the
Some of the member stuff. I'm gonna redo all that and it's gonna look really more more more cultish
Also, I
rebranded the website. I mean, yeah, the website's on its way
Got such cool things on the website as a sigil creator
You can take any desire you have and manifest into a symbol and then like, you know, I can teach you some chaos magic where you can like actually
You know, you basically
will
Create the sigil take a snapshot of this desire connected to the sigil then you'll then you'll forget the sigil. You'll just you'll put it away and
Subconsciously you will make your dreams come true. So make some good wishes, right?
You can look into chaos magic and Austin Osmond spare. He was a very famous magician
Kind of reminds me of mine a little bit where he was actually trained by a real witch
And I know my ex-girlfriend does not like me to call her that but I mean
You have to call a spade a spade
Anyway, just
All I have to say is if you're
Nudigating somebody don't let them
Bring you spaghetti
without
Watching like an actual chef prepare it. You don't know what they're gonna do that spaghetti. You can hide a lot of things in a red sauce, okay?
Just some friendly advice from me. Okay
unfortunately from experience
But
Yeah, I was like when I was like let me see I think about 33 years old I was like
Probably 2012 2013. Yeah
I got to learn magic. I got to learn magic. But part of that was I have to sleep with a woman because
or else I'm not like balanced, right? I shouldn't just say sleep with a woman. I should say, you know,
be in a relationship, whatever. But basically, I slept with her and yeah, I was initiated with
something. I think it was higher. Forget what I was initiated into, okay? But
No, it worked it did work
Let's just say
I've pretty much been celibate
No, it's okay. It was fine. It was good except she turned into a monster and it scared me
But she also turned into a beautiful woman too
So it you know kind of magic worth first both ways, but just like no
You're gonna be like having sex with this hot Indian goddess one second and the next second
Monster, but I mean like you know like there's a movie. What's what's like it has like
Fred Fred
Savage in it was that little monsters
Yeah, she kind of turned into that character
Pretty frightening
Anyway
Enough of my enough of my old stories. So let me see. I think I do have some like new shorts out
Let me see if there's any good new shorts
Not talking about the shorts, you know, my pants. I'm talking about, you know, creating some shorts, so YouTube shorts.
Let me see.
Here's some advice
You know when he was up here with you like psyche. Why did you send me over there?
Why did you do that or why did you play that clip? You know kind of like you know victimizing himself?
You know kind of get sympathy from the panel and you know from everyone and you know not really speaking the truth
Hey homeboy he went over there by himself. You know he asked who it was you corrected him told him the name
He clicked the link you didn't tell him ago
But then that woman shit
Shannon yeah, Shannon I believe that's the one who used to be with LD 15 and she lives not even that far for me
She lives like maybe like 15 20 minutes
Not that far and
Not that far you're also
So yeah, I don't know like as far as like I thought I was too like
Kind of I haven't heard I don't want to you know throw allegations out there, but I haven't heard
Like I haven't heard you know good stuff
So
She sounds like a monster. I mean she was and then I buried did donate for reading so I gave her reading but
You know, I had enough of like people just disparaging my terror reading
It's like, you know, you don't have to get a terror reading from me if you don't want to
Anyway, yeah, that's that story. Okay
That's what we got in our little archive
Here I know what the cards mean, you know, I I have over one thousand eight hundred
Dude, that was bullshit to beat up trying to say oh psyche can't even read the cards, right?
He don't know what he's saying. He gets it going
Doing this and I'm like what the hell psyche reads the cards correctly every time like every time he's reading them
I've seen a reading like it's up to the spot on
And yeah, well the guy um exiled one was saying that oh, I have a video of him years ago
Going on somebody's show. It wasn't him on this platform reported him. So I what that's not even true
I didn't have a webcam until like recently when I spent, you know
I used to do it that of my out of my tablet. Everybody's saying it was years ago
I was on some terror readers program and I didn't know anything about tarot. It's you kept where you can join ghost the link is
I'll put the link up there.
Guys, I just want to say,
guys, the video is really insulting, it is.
Here's the, and these are the specifications,
this tape, okay, so there's a tape out, okay?
He saw this, he saw it, but he doesn't know where it is
or anything, and then he's backed out of the deal
because he said I like insulted Bronzeboro
or something, which is, and soon as you started saying,
Shannon, oh, you're Shannon?
Are you, but are you Shannon, you're not,
you're not that like, that mean Shannon lady,
You're a you know, like basically I think it's cringe cringe the source his mother. I don't know if you know cringe the source, but
You're Shannon. Okay. Well, maybe I got the name. I can remember it and I was like seeing Shannon share
I don't know. Welcome to dad. I'm welcome from deep down the rabbit hole. Hello. I like rabbit holes
I actually have a playing a game right now called down the rabbit hole. It's on BR and
It's pretty cool. I
Have a couple Alice in Wonderland games. I do love Alice in Wonderland, right?
But welcome. Make sure you subscribe. Welcome to the cult, right?
Just gonna be like, you know, basically everyone in the chat is an honorary cult member, right?
You know, honorary, unless we sacrifice them. They can always use an alt, but that's kind of like, you know, reincarnating.
But, yeah.
Everyone's an honorary, but you can become a oh
Yeah, so I also guys you might want to consider really the membership because it's five bucks
But I think I'm gonna start doing more
Members only stuff like members only lives I
could actually
With in the middle of the show I could like switch to a members only and then it will say then
People want to continue watching they can't like so it will that'll be for like, you know to just do member readings or to do like just
member stuff, you know, like we do some students like you know secret like you know
Orgies and freak offs. I'm just kidding. We don't really do that
But we could I just like I'm usually not even invited to my own backstage freak offs like I don't even understand how that works
but
I know I've seen some interesting things. I saw flirty diamonds boobs a few times. Hey Brandon. How are you?
Flirty diamonds boobs. Let me see flirty diamond and auto they they were on recently. This was pretty funny. I don't know if you saw this
What just happened here?
Listen what that beat you your boyfriend
ʻʻʰʰʰʰʰʰʰʰʰʰʰʰʰʰʰʰʰʰʰʰʰʰʰʰʰʰʰʰʰʰʰʰʰʰʰʰʰʰʰʰʰʰʰʰʰʰʰʰʰʰʰʰʰʰʰʰʰʰʰʰʰʰʰʰʰʰʰʰʰʰʰʰʰʰʰʰʰʰʰʰʰʰʰʰʰʰʰʰʰʰʰʰʰʰʰʰʰʰʰʰʰʰʰʰʰʰʰʰʰ
What's up?
I don't know. Let him. Let him.
Oh, my god. He looks good.
He's saying he's saying, you know, pendejo means she's like idiot and then it's like saying pinga, which is dick
And then he's saying chocha, which is vagina. I mean, I speak some Spanish
I don't think he's speaking it the correct way for a Puerto Rican. I'm not very impressed. That's all he knows how to say
Chocha pinga and pendejo. I mean, it's like, I don't even know if those are appropriate
Words and Dominican Republic or wherever he's from I don't know
Yo tengo un grande verga por para mi boca
Anybody oh
Okay, nevermind. Let me just place I
Thought I meant something else. Okay, I meant something
walked alone through shattered skies with nothing left but haunted highs a thousand
no's a million tries still joni's name oh my god the joni song was in my cries
e o papo
The Echoes Drive
So who wants an animal card?
Just I'm going to put, for members,
I'm going to put some cool emojis to get my attention.
But for other people, can just like, yeah,
Nick got my attention with a flex.
If you would like a card, Nick, if you put a flexing arm
on the screen, I'll probably pay attention to it.
But actually, I'm going to make a game in sexier flex.
I'm going to put that as an emoji.
I have all these good ideas.
Your guys are going to love.
the new Psyche Awakens, the new Cult of Psyche website.
I have put a lot of money into it, it's kind of expensive.
But you know what?
You guys are worth it.
I think it's worth it.
It's actually, it'll be great for me to have, you know,
certain service offerings on here.
Oh, we have Apollo Moon Labs.
Hello!
Ha ha ha ha!
Whoa! I'm a fan of Chrissy now!
I love Chrissy, I love Chrissy now. Who the fuck? I never heard about her, but I love the song.
You like the song? Yeah, yeah, thank you. I would have played it, but you know, I had copyright concerns.
But yeah, I thought about you when I saw that I was like, oh, this is perfect for Apollo.
Dang! No, listen, I watch almost all the videos here you post.
on your community page you know because you have to you find some real gems you understand
what I mean yeah I never heard about these artists I never listened to them but I'm open-minded
and this from Chrissy wow I direct I directly downloaded it man I love it
Yeah, she's she's pretty. She kind of has like a lady Gaga like a little bit of a vibe. Yeah
But yeah, I mean, you know, she's got the personality
I don't know. I don't like this kind of woman, you know, with her big lips
They all look the same for me, but the song I love the song. I'm gonna play it to my wife
When she when she come back
Does she call you Apollo or does she call you like by your real or is Apollo your real
name? Listen, listen, my real name, first name is Apollo.
Oh, wow. That's amazing. It is Apollo because you know, my mother had to pay for Greek mythology
and she forced me to study it, you know, and, uh,
Yeah, and one of my sons have also the middle name also Apollo because I love this the name you know here in Germany
The name Apollo back then when I was younger and singer it was an opener for the ladies trust me
Oh, but they're bad, you know.
Yeah, when you go to the ladies, what's your name?
Oh, my name is Sabina.
What's your name?
My name is Apollo.
Dang.
It's an opera, you're already in.
Yeah, I know.
If it was like you and me went out hunting for some chicks
and then I'd be like, oh, I'm John.
And then they were like, oh, Apollo.
And it's like, even if you were like, you know, monster,
you'd probably get more chicks than I would, for sure.
No, I don't say it. I don't say it.
The thing is, I don't know.
Okay, I know you're gay. Okay.
I don't know. Maybe you have your experience with women.
But back then, I think I'm not much older than you.
I think I'm older than you.
Back then it was different types.
You know, women back then was not that entitled.
You know, there were more chill, more...
I don't, I don't know, you know, today women's, you know, entitled right? I know it's all I mean, it's like it's it's like there
It's almost like it reminds me of like, you know
There's people that want like reparations for slavery and they were never slaves, right, right? It's like
Right, it's like there's a certain like, you know
Horrible things that people is like, I don't know maybe their ancestors have gone through or something like that
I think people have been got had it pretty easy these days comparatively to like the past times and
Wow, think about all the strong women like had
Just up this this is like the people that are alive in this world because of a woman
You know if men were in charge of all the babies, I think that they would you know
Yeah, but my wife listen
I'm I'm old school. Okay. I'm old school. I have different views of what a strong woman is and for me all these
screaming hyenas and then
Overdoing shit, you know with makeup and you know
I think some women and I'm not I don't okay some women like
make themselves look like a baby and it's like a subconscious way no no no not that far not that
far okay as an example it's only a second an example okay only an example i'm married i'm
happily married you know i don't want to hit on any online woman but character wise
Okay, she don't start shit. She don't she stay out of any shit. She's not a screamer. She's not cursing
But she still gets away
right
That's a woman for me. Yeah, and if you really tell an elector has been like have I ever had like a
Like a fight with a lecture again. I don't think I've ever like those people that I don't know
No, I never have I mean, it's like, oh, you know, it's like because but have I had a fight with the people?
I've not even had a fight. I've been screamed at like, you know, to me like, you know, oh, yeah
You know, it's this bank. I mean, it's like I mean to feel like a
worse than a like a
Bad kid a child, you know, it's like, I don't know it's like even but even men like, you know, this guy
I'm schooled Athens. I don't know are you familiar with the school of Athens?
No, I'm yet. Okay. So last night he was in my he was on the panel and stuff and
He just kept talking about
Oh ghost, you know, it's like, you know men don't don't need to enter men this amount of money, you know
Like I say Athens, can you like, you know, this is like I just don't like I'm comfortable people talking
But like first of all to my donators like that and then like second of all like about
And it's like oh wait think what wait anything? Oh, yeah, and he just like then he kept going on and on about it eventually like I
I told Jamie to hide him, but I'll forgive him, but it's just like, it's like, and then
I was like, I just don't talk about it, and then I say, he's not respecting me as a host,
like continuing to go on.
And it's almost like a passive aggressive thing, where it's like,
Yeah, yeah, I understand what you mean.
But can I give you, listen, like I said, I don't like to give unwanted advice.
Can I give you my opinion?
Sure.
Some of this man too serious
Man or we or just or just just matter no every woman even some of this woman, you know, well, but
I can only talk about the the people I know because we were back then we were on tvp all of us, okay
The way before I was in the scene like you all were friends, yes
And I know them and I can only judge about these people
No one else. Okay
And like gay bird even school of artens, you know
He he is easy to influence
and
Trust me, he gets brainwashed. All this club of men stay turned, L.A.S., gay,
bird, whatever, smush. They all are brainwashed from the same club of women.
And you're focusing too much on them. They are only lemmings.
They are lemmings. Lemmings. Okay. Yeah, I mean it's like yeah, I mean I
You know where I like I like summer and even though summers like yelled at me and summer sometimes
Little you know like a hot mess, right? She was a little crazy sometimes, but
Yeah, I understand I say and I understand like some people like this is like they're an outlet for a lot of like, you know
Steam or like, you know, just like
Like just like it's like a break from like the regular stuff and she and so yeah, she explained it to me
It's like a new release for her. It's a
Screamer people but you do you know what she got better
She got better they try trust me if people knew who summer or Christine was
Last year, they would be ashamed of
the of them
But I have to admit
lately later, let's say two three months. They got much much better
Much better they improved
You know Christine like, you know, totally hates me now, but maybe like, you know, maybe I was a bad
person around her. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know why she hated me. She hates me because
Crystal Marie was saying some stuff, but it you know, I know you're wrong. You're wrong. It has nothing to do with Crystal Marie
Nothing
Okay, because she's the one she listen. She's the one who always preach have a thick skin on
Penelts and now she's gonna act like a little girl because Chris and Malik or touch up
Talk at some shit about it. Come on now
It has nothing to do with Christian Marie. Trust me, it started all because you took the power from this panel.
And she's a control freak. She likes to control people and she can control panels.
Trust me, your panel is not the first one she made this script.
There was other pennants like money for 20s blah blah blah
Bunch of other pennants she liked to control pennants at as soon she lose the control of the panel
You are the enemy of the scene. It has nothing to do with
Like ever having any kind of conflict over it like I always would like
What up, what up psyche
Follow your line fucking bitch
Ah, okay. Yeah, she don't run. Nobody's panel. He's lying ass nigga
He's saying I don't want to run. Does he want to spend any food?
Yeah, you trying to go your second, you know, it's crazy this little motherfucker on top
He was trying to run my fucking panel tell me what to do
Yeah
That's the type of low IQ, low IQ New York fool.
You're mad, you're buddy, you're buddy got docked.
They all talk about no doxing, no doxing,
and then they all talk about doxing on their pendant.
Ah, I know, they're doxing.
It's funny.
None of these pendant owners follow their own rules.
All they talk, no talk about.
No talk about doxing, and it's exactly what they do.
This New York fool talking about the woman's children and he wanted to fuck them and all these
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
Yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo
You're a bitch
That's the point
They're all taking no talking about kids and this fool
Another woman's kids
What's it talking about kids? That's how you feel stupid motherfucking when I talk about kids like like no no
Doctoring on your pendant, right? And the first thing I thought
Right
Stop the rage happened
Nobody talk about kids you stupid motherfucker. No, no, no one tell ducks on your right. I know what people say in my panel, bro
It's my panel
You are responsible for what?
It's on your panel
Other people do the same thing
What my panel do
You are responsible for what
People say
When you go to other panel
New York
Fat fuck
Grow up
Talk about people
Why you don't say something in New York water seriously. Yes, something is wrong with New York
Is there a woman in the background talking I heard a woman's voice
Not a me. No, I am alone
You got a girl there
That's a pile. Yeah, is there someone in your bed?
I heard again
My my my my woman is on a business trip. I'm alone. No, she's not. No, she's not. She's in my house right now
Oh my god. Oh, she is
It's in my house right now, bitch. It sounds like
like trans dresser
See this New York idiots don't talk the same shit
Hey, I was kissing Apollo
Touch your butt
Can I do a character AI of you and have sex with it?
No.
Oh, no.
No, he likes it, he likes it, he likes it, he likes it, yeah, yeah, I already did Apollo, I did it, I did an episode with Apollo, I made him an episode with Odysseus, I made the character Odysseus, oh yeah, you weren't there that day, I just, we just named it after you, yeah.
Yeah, we have this character. Yeah, yeah, I know what you mean. Yeah, yeah. I remember. I remember you now come back
That's what you want to talk about, so remember, you only use Spanish words and you repeat it.
He's Chupacabra, Chupacabra, he's a chupacabra, he's a chupacabra, he's a chupacabra, he's a chupacabra, he's a chupacabra, he's a chupacabra, he's a chupacabra, he's a chupacabra, he's a chupacabra, he's a chupacabra, he's a chupacabra, he's a chupacabra, he's a chupacabra, he's a chupacabra, he's a chupacabra, he's a chupacabra, he's a chupacabra, he's a chupacabra, he's a chupacabra, he's a chupacabra, he's a chupacabra, he's a chupacabra, he's a chupacabra, he's
After you can have it after you
About you he said he wanted he wanted to do the bang-boom bang-bang
The kids like you get your follow kids
No
Oh my god, that's oh my god
Greek and I got Puerto Rican instead
I'm not skinny motherfucker
People are all the same
Don't go crazy
No, no, no, no, no do that don't do that psyche don't do that
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
On these panels, I can judge only about panels, okay?
On these panels, all New Yorkers are met
a mental, unstable, insecure ladyboy.
Yo, you're a pilot, come over.
Come over to the other side.
Can you both come over at the same time?
I want both of you.
Come over to the other side, you stupid motherfucker.
Just like, just like, see how I'm in between them right now?
Like a-
Kirby, see, Kirby.
This is what I want.
How can anyone any normal human could like someone like like LAS he's like a
No, I do dog. No, I do dog. He repeats the same shit over and over
No, but the dogs, you know, hey, yes, I put peanut butter all over myself. Do you like?
Yo, you you you want you want you want you to get fucked up. Oh, yeah
I like it. I like it.
I like it. I like it. I like it. I like it. I like it. I like it. I like it. I like it.
it. I like it. I like it. I like it. I like it. I like it. I like it. I like it. I like
See, that's what I mean, Psyche.
They bark loud, but they are insecure.
Deep down, these New York foods are all insecure.
Oh my God, you know, okay, so do you know Aldi?
Aldi, his name is Aldi 5K?
No, I think, no.
Let me see, well, there's this person,
their name is Uppi, I think, and they put,
I'll just like, it's like a couple of minute clip,
but this guy, he's like, come on my show,
porn bombing me like several times, right?
And, you know, he's like, you know, he has like a whole like little army of people like that do it to you. And so someone sent me this clip of him like talking to Q and and to blogger.
And he's like, oh my God, psyche, he hit on me. And then I told him, you know, beg for it.
And he started begging. Isn't that like disgusting? I don't know any of these people. Seriously. I don't know any of them.
Well, I'll try to find out for a second. Because it's worth seeing. I mean, it's like...
I mean people are are like, I don't know it's like even this guy who porn balls me
He showed me his balls like several times and then he's like, oh
Yeah, he's he's like he's like stood up and like pulled down his pants a few times and he has like these like
Okay, okay. Listen. I'm a dump European. I'm not that
Experience in this YouTube see do people really show her but their buttholes and the penises. Yeah, do you know?
Well Aldi did, and then Ilya, Ilya Oblomov, who's in the chat, he, he mooned the chat one time, and then all the time he, he said, oh can I be the first guy to pee in like a jug on your stream, and I was like, no you can't do that.
And then I turned my head, he was peeing in a bucket, right, and then he saw us again.
And the third time he came in a kilt and I was like, no, no, you can't like show us under the kill and you kept almost doing it
And then I fell asleep and I woke up and I still had my channel because
He got up to adjust the camera and it turned off. So somehow I
So, yeah, I think I can look up on my phone like this and find this challenge with the tag man. Yeah
This is a fat dish is to show your genitals on on random people
I don't understand. I think it's a fetish. I think he has a fetish for it because I mean he hit the smile on his face
He's just so proud and it's like and then I don't know and then Aldi I don't know why Aldi was doing
I mean, it's like there's nothing really to be proud of weird people weird
And uh, yeah, and it's like oh, and then it's my fault for being gay. Okay, so
Okay, yeah, wait wait one thing listen
I I don't like it, but that's my personal thing when you two when you try to talk the sexual shit with me, but
I couldn't have anything against you being gay, okay?
But I'm not used to it with men hitting on me, okay?
Woman? Okay.
This is normal for me, but not men.
This is strange for me.
I don't know. I don't know.
Well, I mean, I like it.
I like it when men are like, you know.
It's a game for you.
I understand. It's a game for you. I understand.
Yeah, it's a game.
Um, let's see. So they were talking about me, but he's taken down the clip. It looks like oh, but oh, hold on
I found okay, so this is like I'll just play this short little clip and look how insecure these guys are
Well, it's like, you know, and it's Tommy James blogger, and I don't know if you know any of like all of them, but
You don't know
Okay, okay. Well anyway, hopefully it will still be interesting to you. Let me see. Um, there's my history. Okay
Okay, so blogger Aldi and Tommy discuss psyche
Okay, and then there's also another one called failed witch hunts with me in it for some reason. Okay, okay
So check this out of hollow. Let's see share screen. Okay. No, I don't know if I want to see that, but it's not it's not bad
They don't do anything this like this. Yeah, okay. Okay
Here you go. Here you go
Don't don't we both got we both got sexually harassed
Yeah, I'm sorry. Me too. Me too. What?
I swear to god, like he begged me
He begged me to let him suck my dick
Yeah, I got the beer baby, I got the beer baby, I got the beer baby, I got the beer baby, I got the beer baby, I got the beer baby, I got the beer baby, I got the beer baby, I got the beer baby, I got the beer baby, I got the beer baby, I got the beer baby, I got the beer baby, I got the beer baby, I got the beer baby, I got the beer baby, I got the beer baby, I got the beer baby, I got the beer baby, I got the beer baby, I got the beer baby, I got the beer baby, I got the beer baby, I got the beer baby, I got the beer baby, I got the beer baby, I got the beer baby, I got the beer baby, I got the beer baby, I got the beer baby, I got the beer baby, I got the beer baby, I got the beer baby, I got the beer baby, I got the beer baby, I got the beer baby, I got the beer baby
You kept saying, like, I kept saying how you want to suck my dick, and I was like, alright then, beg me, beg me to do it, and then, like, the motherfucker on the roof is begging me to suck my dick.
I didn't think he would do it, but he literally did it.
We didn't fucking bother with victims to sexual harassment that I didn't do.
I did not do that at all. I didn't do that to everybody.
That's all bad. That's all bad.
It was weird, bro. It was very weird.
And then I couldn't help it.
Who do you go and literally ask him to beg for it and ask him if he would do it?
Literally.
Yeah.
He did it.
It's weird.
He was
I was like, hell no, I'm not gonna show my balls and I'll show my dick to be funny, but I'm not gonna show my balls to be funny, but I'm not gonna show my balls to be funny, but I'm not gonna show my balls to be funny, but I'm not gonna show my balls to be funny, but I'm not gonna show my balls to be funny, but I'm not gonna show my balls to be funny, but I'm not gonna show my balls to be funny, but I'm not gonna show my balls to be funny, but I'm not gonna show my balls to be funny, but I'm not gonna show my balls to be funny, but I'm not gonna show my balls to be funny, but I'm not gonna show my balls to be funny, but I'm not gonna show my balls to be funny, but I'm not gonna show my balls to be funny, but I'm not gonna show my balls to be funny, but I'm not gonna show my balls to be funny, but I'm not gonna show my
It's more like kind of weird manipulation, I think, and like, but no, no, I got it easy, sir.
I really did. I was standing there.
Not too bad, honestly. Nothing I could really say, honestly, I guess.
Well, I was just waiting for a look at you.
I was just waiting for a look at you.
Imagine, imagine fighting over these guys.
Evro!
He seemed to like, like, rather than not doing it, so maybe...
And look what they all have in common, Chai, they're drinking alcohol, all of them.
Much of drugs. No. No, it's okay. I drink two of it. I'm just kidding. But I have a
There's one more thing. I haven't seen this club. It said I said
I'm in I'm disgusting it. Um, it says oh that one was age restricted for something. I don't know why though. It's okay. So it says, um,
Let's see. Oh, bury the turtle shows. No, no. Okay. So, um, clumsy, berry cooking. We see Aldi being sus.
Filled with witch heads with Sandman. Okay. Yeah, this is, this is it. I don't think I've watched this one.
Okay, check this out. This is, this is on Uppie's channel, by the way, guys. Uppie is in my chat sometimes.
It's a pretty cool clip channel. Good luck with your clip channel. I like it. Okay, so, um,
uh, let's see. I haven't seen this clip. Let's see.
I don't I don't I don't I don't
I don't. I don't. I don't I don't
No, it's not
While you originally marketing as a children's game is still played by kids
An adult read that y'all. Oh, it was still too big kids. Yes. Yeah
You know my market is a silly game. Yes teenagers. No, I know I would not outplay you know like the furries here in Europe
That's what like, you know
Like well with it, but some of the video game stuff like has like a UVO fucking
Yeah, I think yeah, I think that was kind of a field field which I don't say I mean, but I could never take his motherfuckers seriously ever I
Don't know
What else is going on this
No
What?
That's a problem, that's a problem, that's a problem.
Well, I'm just kidding, I'm just kidding.
Exactly, I agree with you Scott, it's a game.
The box is like, you know, there's something in Brandon who's like, he's actively on the app.
And then he's been at the same everywhere on the Roblox.
What the fuck on Roblox? Anyway, it's like the Minecraft, right?
It's like a Minecraft.
I mean, what the fuck is that?
I have I have some
Right. Well, seriously, I personally have not looked too much into it, but it is like a platform where it's like, I guess, they allow interaction between players, probably more than other...
Like all online games, Warcraft, POE, they all...
There's a problem. I guess there's like people that are trading their kids to like hit on like adults and trying to catch people on or something like that
I don't know like oh
Yeah, that's yeah, that's kind of like I think Alexander's covered a little bit of it like um, and so I don't know what hit
But if you play I mean it's like, you know, there are video games
And I have like over a thousand video games on steam and stuff like that, you know, I um
You know, some of them might be considered kids games and stuff like that or you know, I just got a thousand
Yeah, but but this can happen on all online games. Okay. There's nothing to do with the game itself
There are millions of games online games RPGs that can happen in modern warfare. It can happen in
whatever you know
snap a lead or
Star Wars
It's a card like there's a car game called I guess what is it called her magic the gathering magic
But there's one called hearthstone, and it's kind of like magic the gathering the same kind of
Our game, but it's like you but then you have a player you can play against real players, and it's like
five years old. You have no idea because you're just doing cards and stuff like that.
Usually the kids will win because they're like much better at the game than the kids will.
Oh yeah, tell me about it. I was back then, oh man, now you bring memories back.
Back then I was playing with my son Halo, one businessman. I was considering myself as a good
He was beating me. Yeah, I don't know how these kids are doing it
But they just they're very
It's just like growing up with cell phones and stuff. They just grow up with these games and like, you know, probably
You know, but play video games very young you can pick up a lot of things really quickly, you know, and so
Yeah, but I remember he used to play checkers with my grandfather and he would always like win
I get so mad at him
I'd be like pretending a little bit because it's like he's so much smarter like you know in checker
You know, it's like we're gonna have like five years old and he's like, you know
So you know is so he'd have to like kind of like try to like lose on purpose occasionally, so I didn't get mad
Yeah, war stuff, I know it's like also like the video games nowadays it seems like it's strange
You know the ps2 controller or the Xbox controller is like the same. Yeah layout controller these in the military for like, you know
Some certain worker stuff like for the drones. Yeah for drones and things like that and it's like it's just basically training
you know, like the generations through with the entertainment, also desensitizing to the violence and it's like having like, you know, the ability to unalive someone is one thing if you're doing it like right to the face to face and but if you're doing it over a computer right and you're unalive, you know, and just like sending like, you know, like little blips on the screen and that's
Yeah, I understand what you mean, but that's where parents are for.
To teach the children the children the morals and what's wrong or right, okay? That's my point
Sure, but for me, but for me listen for me today's today
Most parents of today are children themselves. They shouldn't have
Kids yeah make kids and bring them to this world. It's very easy
But we'll make them
let's say
Good human. Yeah, hard. They care of them. Okay, teach them the right things
But most people today with the spitting the children left and right. Oh
My god, like it's it's popcorn. It's popcorn one can hear pop one kid
man
I saw video last time, I saw video last time, a woman, you know, it was a rest video, she had 11 kids from 15 different fathers, baby daddy's, they called them baby daddy's and baby mamas, Jesus man, these are human lives, this is nothing to pop up like popcorn, people have no morals anymore.
Right, but it's then again, it's like morality and like, you know, I mean, there's there's a
People are gonna be experimenting with sex and stuff, but there's a you know
How about like, you know keeping a child or or raising a child of being a father to the child and supporting a child or you know
Just like, you know trying to pay for an abortion that kind of morality, right? Which is like not morality. Yeah
There's Nick. What's Nick doing? Let's see. Oh
Well, he's far away from the camera
What oh, you see him he's walking around doing something. Yeah
He's wearing a lot of clothes. Oh, he's doing some gardening
Okay
Well, yeah, this is yeah, I was yesterday I was yesterday in
In a Halloween gala in in Cologne a gala. Oh, that sounds fancy
But boring as fuck
What did you wear a costume?
Yes
What was your costume? Did you and your wife do it a couple's costume? Yeah. Yeah, I was going as Frankenstein
You know Frankenstein
Were you Frankenstein's monster or the doctor? Yeah, yeah, Frankenstein monster with the pins on his head
I had to I had to do a little bit of makeup, you know my daughter made a makeup for me
That's okay. No, it was for it was not for Halloween. It was more like I
Need to collect some money, you know for something
Yeah, yeah, yes, fundraiser. I need to collect to find donations for something and
I had to go
Yeah
well, you know, it's like
My parents had very act my parents had more had more active social life
And I I mean it's that were that all my brothers and sisters like you know my parents were going out three four times a week and
Halloween parties
But I haven't really celebrate Halloween a while so this will be exciting like you know
I mean, I mean, I don't know if I'll have a special costume
But it's like I mean I'm kind of like I'm trying to dress up all month and beyond you know, I love
Love costumes and like stuff like that. I love if you like my staff. I love the staff
Wait, do do I have an echo? It's my mic from bed. I've tried to fix it. I don't know if it got better
It's a better chat. We have 20 people in chat. I guess it's not sorry
I could try another microphone finding me, but I don't know if then anybody had trouble or anything
This is a cool. This is some really cool cool find
Yeah, shit
Chat it's where my microphone may make a noise or so what happens why anyone complaining?
Um, I don't know that was like they were plenty a few minutes ago, but then I um, I
Adjusts I or I fix it. Okay. Okay
Oh, it was when Aldi was on. I don't know if that was like that with the Aldi clip. Yeah. Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay
Yeah, it was making a lot of noise
But uh, so I'm making a website. I
Mean it's updated and everything. I mean, I can't show you the updated one
But I can show you what it was like before I rebranded a little bit, but I'll show you how it's how it's turning out
Yeah, I want to ask you what's up. It is a rebrand kind of
What do you mean? It's it's a I you say are you some sort of John Jones or what?
John Jones, yeah, I'm John Jones. No, no, it's actually so
So yeah, it's a cool. Okay, so like I said, it's I'm half
It's half a joke
Did you see the video? I'll
This is this is it's not a joke. Okay. I think it's very seriously, but you can take it seriously or not as you want
It's not anything negative. It's not like, you know, it's supposed to be a little bit satirical
Tongue and she's okay. It's but at the same time
I like to get into character and stuff.
And I do kind of take this as a culture
and a family kind of thing, but I don't raise followers.
I raise leaders.
And so I want people here to like eventually
start their own shows or, you know,
at least just become the best version of themselves
they can be.
But I have this little song.
This is my cult of psyche intro song.
So I'll just made this today.
Here you go.
Okay.
Oh never heard
With super chat pricing
That's it, that's it, that's it, good riddance.
We drink the algorithm's war
A good one I like that seriously I like that thank you so much
I like that I'm uh enjoying easy to easy to remember you know right and it's like
that's another good trick though it's like if you're trying to learn something uh take
some of the information you need to memorize if you need to memorize something and put it
into like a song and then like right and then it's like and then you can just listen to it
and you will remember the song you mean songs are just memorable like just go into your
subconscious and all the cool members are here barbell yeah look we have the whole the whole gang
Yeah, and it is I everyone start your own cool. I mean, it's like it's about like, you know, basically I'm
It's like I'm a cult of you know, it's called the psyche. Psyche is not just me. Psyche was like the ancient goddess of like basically
of
She would basically the beauty on earth like she was
Start she was a mortal woman that was um
People started worshiping over Aphrodite and so Aphrodite got really jealous and angry
And then Cupid her son to go like, you know curse Psyche
And psyche means those of the soul and kind of like the you know, the mind right and it's represented by a butterfly and
Hey, look at this on Nick. Yeah, I'm a third. Hold on. What is what am I looking at? Is it? Oh, I thought I was looking at I thought
But it was legs. Yeah, I can't date the cat daddy and the so I got my like my scepter
I'm gonna get a topic. There we go. I have my I'm gonna get it
Some more costumes. I'm gonna be doing more of the the horoscopes and
Actually, I just did a really cool. I'm making these really cool reports
astrology reports
And they incorporate like all of the Sabian symbols.
So there's like 360 of them,
like one for each degree on the Zodiac.
And so everyone has these placements
on some of these symbols.
So I take the symbols and I put them together in songs
and I put them together in stories
and like basically making a life story.
I kind of do want to share this person, but I haven't talked to him, I don't know if I can share it, but...
Okay, listen, it's not an attack or criticism, okay?
But don't you think you play with things who... I don't know, man.
I don't want to get involved with all this magic and all this shit, you know?
I practice magic, okay? I mean, I bet it's like that.
I've I've done ceremonial magic and I've uh, I've
Wow, I've been really
What what's wrong?
No, I don't like it. I don't like because listen my mother back then she she called
Remember when I was young when she called herself a white witch. Okay. Yeah
She's a real old Greek style. Okay, she's practicing this
Huh?
Yeah
Yeah, yes
Yeah, you know, she was reading for all these neighbors and friends
From coffee for you know from Mokka
Turkish from Turkish Mokka all the left of us, you know, and she was reading all this shit
You know and she but she put cards out in the shit
But I don't know and she wanted me to don't get involved
which is, I try to stay aware.
So what's your, what's your astrological sign by the way?
Aquarius your query is okay, so Aquarius is gonna
You know Aquarius they are unconventional and like unusual things sometimes, but they're also with the status quo
They're they're they're basically everybody to put together right and so it's like it's like the collective energy
And so there is like the collective energy. It's not for the collective. It's not for everybody. It's for
People that look for it because that's why it's called the occult because it has to do with like with like the eyes and things like that
It's also like no, it's like noticing things. It's um
It's also
We have spiritual missions that some of us have very different spirits
Some of us are not meant to awake spiritually in certain ways like some of us are meant to like get into our full
power of it some of us are
We'll get into trouble with it right it's like there's certain that there are a lot of pitfalls and traps and things like that
It's also there's lots of love things that are counterintuitive
Which makes it really hard because we're dealing with things that have to do with intuition and things
But it's like things that you would think
Would work don't work and things that you wouldn't think work would do work. And so it's I mean it's like it's very interesting
It's like a lot of it. It's like I think of it like a science kind of like you make no chance so far
You make no sense to me
Okay, never mind never mind. I don't know. Maybe made sense to me
No, maybe it's me. Maybe it's me. I don't know
No, I'm saying you're maybe some people are not making it. It's the occult occult means hidden, right?
I mean, it's like yeah, yeah, I mean
And it's like in every religion there's gonna be the exoteric, which is like, you know all like the
The Vatican and like the the robes and the jewels
Yeah, the things in the Bible and then they'll be the esoteric which is like a smaller amount of people be initiated into that
Right, and it's like like a Kabbalah is like esoteric Judaism and like then you know
Mahayana is like the
esoteric Buddhism, and then they have, you know, Christian science or maybe even Mormonism would be
considered some kind of esoteric form of Christianity, or you know, and there's also the secrets within
Christianity itself. But so yeah, there's like an inner, there's an inner
like courtyard in a lot of these religions
that can be traversed.
And it's like, but again, with religion,
I think religion is kind of like a boat.
It's like, you can call it like a canoe or something.
And it's like, you wanna have a strong canoe
and have it strong enough to be able to take you
across the water.
But when you get across the water to the other side,
you don't really need to carry the canoe around with you.
In fact, it would be very cumbersome
and like not very practical to carry it around with you.
So it's like, you can get to the shore
and then
You've kind of like integrated the lessons and and and taken the journey on it, right? But it's like you don't need to like a
Lot of it's just mind control, right? A lot of it's just programming to hopefully to be a better person, right? But oh, yeah, trust me
Back then when I was really really active working, okay, I got what?
But hold on one second. It's not in the door. Hello. Oh
I don't have any scrap metal. I'm sorry. Oh
Shit, yeah, the person is I put my name in the article. Hey, I got this guy
It was very nice. He was very nice. I'm Asian man
He's looking a little old little age many probably in his 70s
He's like I was here last week and he's like and he was like he's I just talked to you today
He's like you got the stuff that I was like
I was like, no, I don't have any scrap metal somebody else put the my name in the thing
He's like, oh my he's a he's a I just drove like 30 minutes from like, you know, like a like another city and I mean
It's like he drove
To go to pick up some like scrap metal or freed lawnmower or whatever he thought I have someone put my name in that Craigslist
I don't have anything. I'm sorry
Gosh seriously now that's what you have to deal with
Oh all day, yeah
And people really think this is funny
It's not I mean it's like it's not even like it's not even it's like to me
It's like uh, I mean it's like I feel I feel bad for these people because they're nice people
They're they're just being told there's something free or you know, it's like there's you know
They're just being like, you know used by some like
some uh some
Psychopath, no, I know that the scrap metal guys are just victims
You know they get trolled you but
Whoever make this shit, you know whoever makes this called come on man grow up
We know it is. Okay. Okay. I I understand you. You don't like size
Maybe some people ever don't like me, but is it worth it?
for what
Just because they didn't like me and it's like it's okay cuz if you're okay, so what?
Well, hey me it just means that it's like, you know, I'm getting all the spectrum of people
You know, it's like I'm getting if you're gonna be if I'm gonna be loved. I'm gonna be hated as well, right?
It's like there's gonna be
I think about every celebrity the celebrity can be as nice charming beautiful talented
Kind as is anything and there's gonna be people that just like don't like their face, right?
And they're like or just are jealous or or something and or they get obsessed
Well, and it's like that's all they can do is you know bother somebody else
But it's sad and it's like, you know, let's like say a prayer for them that they're gonna like you know
Get the help they need someday because they're really unhinged and frankly
You know see that's the point. I was trying to make to this LAS idiot. Okay, all these days
You know, you talk no dog seeing no talking about kids
And I joined at his panel and then I saw someone on the on the chat
Putting the number of someone they don't like
Okay, so okay. I understand you don't like him
But if you have a rule, no doxing, it doesn't matter if you like someone or not.
No doxing means no doxing. Point, period.
Right, I mean, yeah, and it's like, you know, and then there's like different things that people are like
Oh, someone says a name. It's doxy someone says
Like the first name last I mean it's like sometimes people's names are already out there sometimes
They've already been doxed in it, but it's like it there. Yeah, so but so I you know
It's like and some people are public figures because like they are like, you know
Putting themselves on YouTube hosting a show, right? It's so what?
Well, that doesn't mean that doesn't mean you can make whatever you want with them.
Come on.
Who raised you?
That's the problem.
I know you are American, you're gonna like, you're not gonna like what I have to say,
but I don't mean it in general, okay?
My opinion is what I learned from all these panels, man, who raised these people?
Animate? Wolves in the woods?
Wolves in the woods, yeah. I mean, basically Rome, yes.
Rome is like the Lupercalia.
Yeah, Rome, Lutz and Rome, I know.
Yeah, but you understand what I mean, you know?
You don't have any morals, you don't have any standards.
You, come on.
I had this discussion with someone, okay?
I understand it's a release for her and I told you, I tried to explain myself to her.
I only go to against people who go below the bed.
Anything else? I don't care.
Scream, curse at them, bitch, f-word, whatever, f-word, whatever you American use.
But don't use kids, don't dogs.
That's that's the only reason why I joined it is better because back then
You know, it's only example. I'm not bitching at it somehow or whatever. It was it's history. It's in the past
But back then some market Christine former the group of
Animals they behaved literally like animals. They wanted to ask for
People they wanted to kill someone's people. They want to strangle them. They want to burn crosses in
In front of the houses and I asked back them and shit to look most horrible shit
Right, I know I mean it is terrible and you know
Like I don't think that's like she's ever KZ use are still you're you're in the you're in trouble with the cult KZ you need to
Casey keeps asking for the link. He wants to come up with a link and Casey is letting come up. Well, what's wrong with him?
I don't know him. What you went into
Alisa Jordana's and said that I was saying bad things about her and
You know nothing with my friendships and things like that
And then I said he has a bit $25 if you want to come up and I've been saying it for weeks and then he
Refuses to pay and just pretend like he didn't hear me say it. So I
Don't know about it. I don't know
Okay. Well, anyway, he think I'm up to pay 25 dollars to my cash. Oh
That's your thing. That's your thing. I don't know. Yeah, I
Don't want to get involved in in more bullshit. Okay. I tried to stay out of it. Well, I had my own
fights to fight and
I'm lucky that I stand alone
Against the disabled group and he said that and I saw
Changes finally assault changes for the better and this my and I don't I have to say it
It makes me happy to see the changes for the better. It makes me happy
So all the work I put in it
It pays out
Yeah, well
You know good energy put in the world welcome back to you and so I'm not trying to extort you please
I mean, how can you start?
Someone that has given nothing. I don't understand but anyway
Okay, Z. Anyway
So what's up today? It is a Sunday. We're having a nice Sunday. This is Sunday. This is $25
25 bucks. Yeah, Alex paid it. I was paid 30
Because he took our money to come as a fine because he poured on me and then he doxxed
Yeah
Yeah, no link for me no link or lonely for you couldn't even if you wanted you've been a tough month
Okay, but you could like, you know if you were to like send $5 or become a member or things like that
That might even be a good start
But it's like yes, make the first step make the first step and show some good will
Yeah, because he's not gonna get will he's gonna sit up here with his burping microphone and
Bitch at me and stuff and now he's mad and he's also posted very rude things on like on my thing the comments
Alex did wrong you just went with the group tour
I you did wrong Casey because you went into at least a Jordanus
Discord which I asked her I put myself online asked her let you back in there because she already had kicked you out
Because she's she's smart and she knew you shouldn't have been in there
But she'd let you back on and then the only thing I ever saw you post was
Um, oh, do you know psyche is talking bad about you saying he's a better streamer than you and blah blah blah blah and
And so if I don't think I have a problem with alisa and alisa like new she's like
Oh, I figured he was like the nut like that's what she said immediately, but um, just that you would uh, you know
You're still in there. Okay. Well, great, you know
No, congratulations, but you know, she she's aware of your thumb nut
I'm a Kermitarian and I will I can I can get your your your name in pink real quick
Yeah, he has trash audio
You did laugh it off it. What does she get it? What does she get any room my relationship?
And then what like what what that that's like what you see but but but auto can happen size remember
I had bet all the two
Uh, you know when I first joined your panel that you kick at me and that's okay. I don't cry about it
My audio was bad. You kick at me. Okay. Say la vie
Yeah, I mean, it's like, yeah, it's like and I'm really it's like I'm gonna take more of the cult leader mentality and it's like
Don't like it. Well
We'll sacrifice you to the cult. Okay. Oh
shit
Yeah
My mods and see the wrenches are actually they're actually like these like you know
you know these these
Death tools that they can use to like just send somebody to the abyss if they annoy everybody too much
Use it, but mods, you know your mod, you know you have the power to do it
That's one thing I don't understand at all these Spanish people make a big thing about these wrenches, man
Some people are branch addicts. It's like fentanyl for them
It's like seriously how low
How broken your ego have to be to feel better having in a branch
Oh, I know it's like and I feel bad because I mean, I'd say I understand because I would like
Did I would say if somebody like I'm modded me I'd be like hey, well, I thought I was friend
You know, it's like so it's like sometimes it feels like and but then it's like people not understood like I've had to unmod everybody because
I've had rogue mods and I've had to like just unmod everybody and then remod everybody and stuff
And so it's not anything personal. I mean, it's like but if people take it personally, so I understand
so I mean
So I try to like mod people that but then it's like, you know, I would prefer like, you know
the mods like, you know, at least be members and stuff like that because
You know, I need to show that, you know, I'm not some joke, you know, but it's I mean, I understand
It's like I've been slandered so much that people think I'm like no the thing is I don't I like to analyze people and situation
The way I see it you put work on this phone on your show. Okay, you put work on show and
Obviously you want to make money nothing wrong with that
I don't think why not make money you put
You go online for so many hours try to to make it interesting for people, you know
Right, why not making money? Why not making money?
I mean what even why not it's like because I mean it's like I don't know because people just have such as such a problem with
Anybody making and I want other people to make money on it, too
I'm like forever. I'm for I think people in this community are like not
Monetizing enough and I come from a marketing background
And so I do I'm aware of like certain like affiliate marketing or or even just self-promotion
I'm working myself and having
This is where I putting my energy and my love and my attention and my focus and everything
And it's like I and I've basically given away a lot, you know, and also I
I'm I don't know how long I'll be here. You know, it's like I'm trying to be as long as I can I'm getting pressure to do
A lot of other things, you know, but it's like this is what I want to do
And so I'm holding my holding my ground and trying to do it, but it's like if it gets to a point where it's like I
Mean, I'm in a pretty low spot right even I just had 300,000 views, but you know, but it's like I even like
the amount of likes I get is like
Not very good. It's like compared to the amount of people watching it's just like a lot of
A lot of people watching that are not apparently very fond of me because they get a lot of dislikes and a lot of like
You know in this hardly any light if I go to tick-tock and do readings and stuff like that
I get people can do most like multiple times, but I get thousands of likes, you know like thousands
And so it's like then it's like I'm here and get like you've got for like six hours, and then you like ten likes
It's like, uh-oh like I'm like either like just like hated or
I don't know, it's kind of disheartening sometimes,
but I believe that I can turn things around.
I really do believe I can turn things around
and things will get better.
And I'm not gonna fret about it.
I'm just gonna keep doing me, keep enjoying.
uh doing what i'm doing you can't you know i don't say no it's something you you can't make
anyone happy and if you and with people i'm gonna find always something to pitch about
especially in this community they're going to pitch about the smallest thing
the dumbest thing it's something it's like yeah and it's like i mean and they do i mean it's like
Then they're like they're yelling at ghosts and ghosts honestly has like
Save the show basically. Okay. Like I mean, it's like he
The reason I have a computer the reason I I have the green screen and like I'm I'm you know eating well and stuff like that
Like ghosts like really stepped up and like that's why and so that's why I let him
Run around and be wild and people complain. It's like people complain that are not even members, you know
really like
Really stepped up for me. And so it's like and so I'm gonna be protective of him and it's like, oh
Just care about me. I don't just care about money, but you know, I want to have why not?
I watch it something be something on pennants, okay?
And that's why I like the late summer, the new summer, because when Christine tried to manipulate people on Beta's panel to attack Ghost because he's spending money on you, okay?
She came up and tried to tell Christine, stop it, it's going to fall back on my panel, and she is right, I was thinking how does she mean that, and I think I understand because summer has also money trolling or whatever system, okay?
So imagine I go there, or you, and attack the donations of Christine and Summer.
Would she like that? No, right and Christine is a financial troll. I mean Christine is like, you know, you know
Got you off a bunch of times and you know and other people and it's up
And so she's like isn't to the systems and stuff like that
She also I don't know but this bit she's saying this because I mentioned this base surfer or not base
Is it what was this guy? There's some guys are gonna. There's some guy named
Blade or something that she was like donating a lot to
Like so he'd like you know by alcohol or something like that until I was saying
Oh
I know what I tried to say is why attack each other the natives
It makes no point any sense. It doesn't make any sense to me
It doesn't make any sense and it's like it just has to be jealousy because even like school bath and when he was saying oh
We know what you know?
You don't have to think you've run this show. Well, it's like
We're only let me run about we're worried about running the show and like yeah, but don't don't don't
Don't think about
He's easy about school. He's easy to go to manipulate and to control
It's easy to manipulate or control
It just seemed like then I say I say give things or give it a rest like stop talking about it
And then he won't and then he's like laughing like I and then he said oh
He's like the shows on life support and so that's when I just got annoyed and I was like, okay
Just hide him because it's like I mean I I'm honest psych. Yes ghost is annoying. Okay
But who isn't I am annoying you are annoying. Anyone is annoying for someone
Yeah, I mean, we're you don't like it. You don't like it. Bye
I love you. It's your fun. Yeah. I know we're all very annoying people, right?
We can't make anyone that loves me look at the chat, you know, he meant all she's doing spreading a negative
Negative with negative energy about me. Should I be I can't make anyone happy. It's nothing
I don't want to make anyone happy
Right well, I mean you know as long as we have to really make ourselves happy and the people we love we want happy to it's like
You know
But and I don't want to make people like you know
You know I'm happy, but I mean it's like I really care if I'm making a troll unhappy
No, but I want to make people that are here for me happy, you know people that are like, you know
like actually fuck with me in a good way rather than like you know secretly hate me and buddy troll and
stuff like that i really you know and yeah that's the point size you know that's what i don't like on
christine she plays a good woman the the quiet one and blah blah blah but if you're really analyzing
control other people, control other panels, control, control, and like I said before,
she tried to hire other low IQ idiots, like gay birds, LAS, and all these other low IQ
idiots to attack people for her.
How to say it to hire
Godi yeah, thank you. Yeah, trust me. Hey, you should attack
She mentioned my name
He and Godi was the first one who
Who refused it?
Yeah, I know and he's like I respect God. He's like is that is a stand-up individual and I'm sure other people would refuse too
like I know like that she's
For you know, it's a fresher people don't know who Christine really are. Yeah, they don't know
I said they fall for the masquerade for the facade
But they're gonna learn it. They trust me so far after some time you learn it it beta gonna learn it too soon
Right, I know I know her character better than herself
Well, there's a bunch of people up on Bita's panel right now that I'm like, Bita, I told Bita, I was like, you're surrounded by some not great people, and I'm just basing that on how they treated me, and how they...
Oh, she's holding herself really good. I think she's doing a good job. For me, I think, for her alone, she's doing a good job. She tried to control a panel lately, okay?
Yeah, I mean I don't think she's a I don't understand why you two don't go along. Why what the fuck was wrong with you people?
It's because she
Has continued to do this like if I approach her in a sad state
He responds in a happy way and then if I come if I come to her in a
Happy state she responds to me in a very negative way, and it's like and then it's just based on
Basically how I approach it and it's like okay if it's gonna be like that kind of op it
It's just like too maddening to have it always the opposite. It's like always
always
Opposing and it's like and I was like and then it's like other people also getting involved and like her listening to other people
There's a point like you boost off boy poison it
You go boost got you listen into snakes
that's why it's so complicated
relationship without getting into other people's relations, like right, it's like, you know,
then it's like, then it gets impossible for me because like, it's like, then people want
you to take sides, people want you to like defend them, they're like, oh, you're better
for this friend than this friend. And it's like, I just want to like everyone to get
along basically. And it's like, but sometimes I guess it's like, you know, it's not always
going to happen. But, um, you know,
I want to I maybe I mean it's like I don't think I think we're past the point of like ever reconciling
Because she just turned on me for so many months like so hard
But you know I whatever I mean is they I don't have ill will or
Okay, I don't want to get too too deep involved, but come on. I never hear
speak
Negatively about you
You never have well, I mean I haven't she's done
Yes, you well you are because she has okay negative negative and also like not very
Not very empathetic sometimes okay, but okay, maybe okay, maybe I'm wrong, okay
Maybe this is her personality and I know she's you know people have been through different things in life
And it's like I'm just I'm willing to like you're okay
If I couldn't make her laugh by putting on the week being a Patriot wig if I couldn't they make her smile by like you know
Sending a cute emoji
Whatever and it's they and said she's like oh never contact me again
Responding to like you know love with like you know hate or whatever that it's like okay, then I'm just gonna
Let her figure stuff out for herself and it's like it's but my door is always. Yes
Sometimes sometimes it's better to do to let the fear let them figure it out by themselves. You're right
yeah, and
So I mean it's like I I want to be a you know
People's lives. I want to be their friend and stuff like that, but I'm not gonna force myself and I'm not yeah exactly
so
Sometimes I do and people say, oh, you're obsessed with all these women and stuff like that. It's like
Friendships and stuff and gay guys and women have different different kind of
Relationship dynamics and straight men and women it's not like a case of like a straight guy like trying to have sex with this woman
It's okay. It's a case of me just having a complicated friendship with some people sometimes and
and nothing people are thinking I'm some kind of monster and
A bully and bullying women and stuff and it's not true and it's annoying that people are
Painting narratives, but you can't really help
The narratives people will paint, you know, it's like all I can do is yeah, yeah
right
so
I will I have another song for you. Let's see if you like this one apollo. This is the
No, don't don't make song about me to fuck. No, it's not about you. It's it's a song. Let me see. I think it's this one
Oh
My god
I don't think it's that one. Okay, I think it's this one
Video file. Okay. I think you'll like this one. This is called. I think it's called stronger. Okay
I was just as lost as you
Don't flinch, I've got the scars to prove it through
A doorway cracked inside my skull
Let the shadowings crawl
Whisper in fall
Every thought but I
Okay
MASH GLURDICS
Out of the dream, slow, quiet
Not giving up
nice one. I like the lyrics. The lyrics are really empowering. I love it.
Thank you. I think it makes me feel stronger. It does. It's like I'm feeling and I'm feeling
like also like the show is getting stronger. I'm like, you know what, here's like an analogy.
Like I was I'm trying to build this website.
And the the site I'm using took it. It was like, okay
Well, no set up all this stuff on some other websites
So go to the other websites and try to set up and it was like just a nightmare
I say and then I couldn't get anything working and then I it just didn't work
It didn't work it didn't work and I kept going back and forth and trying to get it and it didn't and then
Eventually I was like, okay, so then I was like so far into it
I was like, okay, what do I do now and I was like, okay. Well either I just like
So I went back to the original thing and I was like,
can we do this all within you
instead of like going to the outside store?
And I was like, yeah, I can do it.
And so I didn't even have to go to those outside.
It's like, I just wasted this time
going to these other things.
And it's like, they didn't work.
And so instead of just like staying,
like, you know, I can just try forever
and I'm just going forever or I can just like,
see if there's another solution.
And it's like, and like, you know,
I don't have to go.
to all these other things and places.
But take a break, maybe let it go for a little bit, you know?
Well, yeah, and I'm thinking like I'm going to be placing
on like this new website I've been doing,
it's going to have really like a lot of cool things.
Like it will have free readings, it will have astrology.
Like, you know, you can put it, you can make sigils on it.
I think it is, yeah, sure.
Hey, what's up? So I have like cool thing and I'm like putting a lot of work into it and it's like and I'm gonna basically
Have my show be a more special thing my show beyond less. It'll be on like it'll be like maybe a couple hours
like maybe four times a week or something like that and
Maybe I think it will be like less is more in a way
I think I've maybe I put myself up like you know too much out there a little bit and then people are like
Oh my gosh this guy like they're you know, and they and it's like I'm being putting him too much in your face
And so it's like I'm gonna like step back and let people come to me
And it's like and I really am getting like less of the
horrible trolling and like I'm getting like a lot like a lot of people are coming back and stuff like that and
It's like I like the energy better. It's it's gonna get better again. You know, it's like I mean
I've had some low points in this YouTube thing. I've had I've had angels to it's like really it's like
Just when I think, oh, no one cares, no, like, then it's like, someone like Ghost comes along, really like, really, really helps, helps out and it's like, changes the game in a certain way for me.
And will help me to like, it's like...
Exactly, that's what I said, you know, also from chat, okay? People complaining about...
Let us an example me. Let's take me as an example. Yeah, oh this fucking German. What else like he man
You know, what are you sir doing here? If you don't like it, okay?
If you don't like what I have to say come up and try to change the subject do it better than me
Do it better than me other than complaining in chat
Right. I mean, that's why I have panels and it's like, you know, and also sometimes I'll just be doing what I want and people will be like
Well, what are you like, you know, it's like I'm doing what I want to do. And so it's like and ultimately it's gonna be my rules
And it's like I have to be unapologetic and people say oh, that's like cold or he's an asshole about it
But it's like really that's why I encourage everyone start your own show and see how it. Yeah
Yeah, how hot it is
I truly believe it's not that easy that I will never do what you people do what
beta is doing what you are doing what Eli is doing what we're somebody's doing
no never ever I will never put this pressure on myself never ever
Jesus it's not that easy and it is it is work and it is like and it's like you
know anything if it wasn't work I mean it's like I wish I could like just be
I don't need to make any,
I can just do this completely for fun and like, whoa, blah.
And I could, I mean, yeah, I would like,
that would be, you know, anybody's goal,
but it's like, it also,
it takes work to build something that YouTube success.
Do you know that 1% of,
like maybe 5% of channels are even like, you know,
putting out content and of those channels
to put out content, 1% ever get monetized.
And so it's like such a small percentage of people that even get monetized or make any money
It's like it's very difficult to do and it's like and I've done it. I mean, I'm doing it. I mean, I'm I'm
Yeah, but but you know what but I mean
This penalty holes are under constant pressure
To how to say it to keep it interesting for people, you know, and I like to keep it
I like to like have some of the drama community and everything it's just like
It can't have my own thing to do.
I have my own thing to do.
I have my own vision of this.
I can't be distracted by like,
because a lot of trolling is just distraction
to get you off into there.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, off into there.
I mean, it's like, and so it's like,
I got to stay focused.
I want to be helping people.
I want to like have a show that helps other pan,
and the website, I want to like, you know,
have this website be something that is like,
almost like an IP two.
But it's like, you know, of like actually like really, like, you know,
I think it's going to be maybe we'll have two people on it, but it will be.
Not something where it's like, oh, it's about like, you know, making people low cows. It's about being mean
It's about macing the homeless people and I mean, I think some of some of there's so much negativity that's come along with it
Right that so I want to make it up. I want to make a more positive thing where we'll do the same thing
I'll have a website that will show when people are alive
But it'll actually be people that want to go support different people people that are interested in like different
Topics and all kinds of things that people would love this panel for I mean it's like this is like a little small like tiny like little
Little piece of this whole like entire YouTube panel thing and we're just in this tiny little
the slice of it like just like you know like thousands of people probably like maybe 20,000
people at most or something think about there's like eight billion people in the world think
about how many people would like love there are people people that would consider even like you
know the least of the panel versus like some kind of celebrity if they were like they'll be like oh
my god that person amazing they're like talking on a camera with a chat and I mean it's like
but it's hard to reach the people who who share the same values like you
It's hard to reach them that's marketing that that's where the marketing comes in
That's why I'm like and that's also like why I'm on different social media
I'm putting myself out there meeting people and and doing everything on different platforms
I'm putting out books and putting out videos and there's so many things that people can possibly find me with that
It's like I'm gonna bring people into this panel verse and it's like I want to share
People that I've met here are great people, but there's people that I think I've met here that have not been so great people too
So it's like I get the opportunity to like, you know
have a site and it's like, you know, it's like
People want to be on it. Like I think it will be a positive thing. It's I think it'll be I don't know. It's basically
you'll have a free version here and so one thing I learned it from you from going on these panels
Yes, and I know that that is nothing new for you. Okay
But man as a best example, okay, because that's how we are here in Europe
Talking we're talking in examples. Okay. Yes. That's how I I agree. I use examples to make my my
My point more more clear as an example
few days ago some of us doing a good thing okay and not much people in my
opinion showed up okay and then you see all these other panels you know I went
to another panel at the same time okay
much more activity, much more fuels.
And all they were talking about, about someone's dog,
someone's cat, someone's nades,
someone's whatever, you know, the most dumb shit.
People are more interested in stupidity.
People are interested in stupidity.
But you know what, that's also a marketing thing.
And it's like, I think that it's like,
some of them just have had better.
Look with marketing or just bringing in certain communities and it's like, but you know what you really want the quality people
I think that summer does no quality people and then it has a bit. Yeah, she's she's gonna blow up more than
It means that she has I mean, I it's like, you know
Especially when you see a beautiful woman, right?
It's like beautiful women it's like not really she's not that beautiful. Yeah, well, I think she I think she's lovely
It's like, you know
That's opinion. That's opinion. That's gusto. They'll be calling it gusto. Yeah
So it's a little bit marketing right and I think I can help her and it's like I can
And I do support her cause and I support and I do think she's a great cause of people are looking, you know
Yes, yes, I agree. Yeah, and it's like but and I think I think personally I'm a good cause too
And I think you know, I mean there there's but you but that's up to people to decide
It's not anybody to tell you or pressure you or to like, you know, there's people there's people actively trying to like, you know
Harass people's donators and things like that and it's not right. It's so stupid
after I hear that on beta spender
Come on Christine. Why do you care who who goes gives his money to?
You have your own pen and imagine I go there and attack attack your
Donators
Right. Well, was she like that? No, she was not and it's a and I'll plus I'm help
I'm trying to help summer too
And I think if she loves summer, you know, it's like I do know some of my marketing
And I and it's like she all she all means like the think god summer is like
You know not
She's not in the bullshit like she like if she'll tell it like it is again. So if Christine's being done
No, she was trust me. That's it. That's your point. It's okay. You didn't have to agree with no one have to agree with me
I have my own. I'm my own. I have my own mind about things. I don't follow no one
She wasn't
The person she's now
Understand that part but like as for me like
think like in this past she has been very fair like she has been like if like
something is bullshit she'll call it as bullshit she won't say she won't just
like take the perfect yeah not always trust me not always she she went a lot
of times too far way too far way too far I don't want to start about talking
about it okay it's gossip I left it behind okay
But because, like I told you in their own panel, you can't fail if you don't try.
And you try to make yourself better.
People like Christine keep the hate inside and she's staying in this hate cycle.
She don't want to get out of this hate cycle.
Well, you know what she should and she should also, you know, now she can't I think I don't know
But you know what I noticed like there's this been there's been this change and it's with some certain people and they just gotten so hateful and
It's just like their personalities have changed
I don't know maybe they switched on me or something like that
But also I see them so sweet and nice to each other
Yeah, okay, listen, I don't care. I'm not here to do to go to lick your ass or whatever how you call it
Okay, I know you don't like criticism with I it's not a criticism. It's only my opinion. Okay
You you love to poke I love to poke too
You love to poke people and to go to get a reaction. So don't play the innocent
Gandhi you're not innocent. Okay, you love to poke but so far. I know you never went under the belt
right I
Poke in a plate like what I consider a playful way and it's like not in a way to like yeah, okay
It's like trying to like, you know
Be a term of endearment in some ways, but I guess it's not taken like that
And so I need to examine maybe my behavior and things like that, but I don't think I've tried to like hurt anybody
I don't think I've
Try to harass anybody. I don't think I tried to bring negativity to anybody or wish anybody harm
I I
Like I honestly love people and it just hurt me like that people turn on me sometimes, but
You know, it's like not everyone's gonna I'm not gonna be everyone's because most people are easy to manipulate
They are seriously anyone prefer flex their chest anyone try to play the most smart ones and
Anyone try to play that like they say in New York losers all of them try to play the top guy gangster
You know and in the end most of them a little mama boys
Yeah, you know
They're easy to manipulate.
I know and it's like but it is sad though. It's like I'd like to
you know
Know who I'm dealing with and stuff and it's like
And have people also strong enough to be their own own person and not just like turn on me because
Other people turn on me, right? So, oh well
Yeah, that's a slavie. It's a slavie
They love me
You know, what is it? Yeah, okay, sir. Oh, uh, okay, sir. Oh, sir. Oh, yeah
Like what I can only but and there's also a great saying at the I think it's a I think it's a Bible versus site
Lord show me
What I
You know can do and what I cannot like what I do not have power over and let me not worry about what's it got?
The serenity prayers like that. Yeah
Exactly, but yeah, let me just let me just worry about things. I have control of and think that I'll have control of
You know, I'm gonna leave to leave to God and the
angels and things like that
For me it seems like people come on this planet to find something to to be offended. I call this
discourage
Yeah, they try to find the most stupid shit to feel offended to make their own miserable life
look better
You know man
Right, and it's a very easy to be a bit. It's if you come here. I am actively offending people. I'm not like, you know
even hiding it. I
Right, I will and I am a different kind of person too and
Not everyone's cup of tea, but you know, I'm a very loyal person. I'm not gonna
I'm not gonna just turn on you because somebody else said oh, I don't like this person
I'm gonna give people a really big opportunity to let redeem themselves as well. I do believe in redemption
I believe we can all do better and, you know, we can all do, and I will also do nobody's
perfect.
I know, I know, trust me, I don't, for myself, I don't pretend to be the most, the best human
on earth, okay?
I know I have a fault, is it the right word, fault?
of one of these Christine Lemmings, you know, Chris, Jesus, the shit he said about children,
Failed yeah fucked up. Yeah
about dead mothers, Jesus. I don't want to repeat it, okay? But for some reason,
I poke him every day. Every day I met him on panel. I poke him, and he never falls back.
And this is surprising for me. How can a human make a... change himself so much?
And this is going along with what you said. People deserve a second chance.
Wait because we're even a different person day if you think about we have like a probably a billion thoughts rushed through our head
You know several at the same time every day just think about have the opportunity for change of
Certain thoughts can have an art. How about have positive thoughts and change for the positive continually?
Sorry, sorry some people asking for the link. I don't know these people
Okay, well, let's see who's asking for late my really gay Arthur. I've seen you Arthur Arthur you what you're are you interested?
Don't ask
Arthur I like a little I know he's engaged, but you know
You don't tell him tell her anything
I support I support a healthy to go ahead. I'm not gonna I'm not gonna bother anybody's marriage. I promise. Okay. I will not
I'm very for a very pro. Oh my goodness thing. It is Katrina is in the chat. This woman is obsessed with me
Help me. Someone need to help me. I need to get rid of Katrina, man. Katrina. You want some uh,
want some uh, Greek uh, I
Don't know man. I know we Greeks have this mojo. Okay, but I can't help it. It's natural
Yeah, I can't get rid of
Do you want some of that Uso? Do you want some of Uso from me?
I hate Uso. Oh, I really hate Uso. I don't like it at all now.
Well, not bad.
It's a black licorice a little bit, right?
Yeah, anise. We call it, it's made from anise.
Please don't talk about anise. I'm trying to...
Oh Jesus you're there you need to I don't know man I don't want to get personal but you need to
You need to have some bang bang. Are you are you interested in Apollo? No
No, shut up. No
You don't shut up. Shut up. It doesn't mean shut up. You're my you're my cult
Get over in the corner. Shut the fuck. No, leave me alone. No, no, here think that is think you this is he trusted
He said
Yes
Yes, are you ready? Yeah, he was praising you. You know, I think
Psycho is a good-looking
I got form bombed, okay, what happened? He said be black dick. Yeah. Oh Jesus